[
  {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
   {
        "right": "cooks",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "cook",
            "are cooking",
            "is cooking"
          ]
        },
        "question": "This week Barbara is away on business so Tom ... dinner for himself.",
  },
 {
        "right": "has been resting - has been",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "has rested - has been being",
            "has been resting - has been being",
            "has rested - has been"
          ]
        },
        "question": "Mary...(rest) in the garden all day because she ... (be) ill.",
  },
 {
        "right": "How",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "What",
            "Why",
            "When"
          ]
        },
        "question": "...did the writer feel? Angry",
  },
 {
        "right": "has not been speaking",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "have spoken",
            "has spoken",
            "have not been speaking"
          ]
        },
        "question": "He ...(not/speak) on the phone for half an hour, just a couple of minutes.",
  },
 {
        "right": "for ten years",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "ten years ago",
            "since ten years",
            "for ten years ago"
          ]
        },
        "question": "He has been selling motorcrycles...?,
  },
 {
        "right": "discovered",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "has discovered",
            "had discovered",
            "discovers"
          ]
        },
        "question": "Columbus.... America more than 400 years ago.",
  },
 {
        "right": "was running",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "run",
            "runs",
            "had run"
          ]
        },
        "question": "He fell down when he.... towards the church.",
  },
 {
        "right": "were still living",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "still lived",
            "still lives",
            "was still living"
          ]
        },
        "question": "We....there when our father died",
  },
 {
        "right": "will be play",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "will play",
            "play",
            "would play"
          ]
        },
        "question": "children...ping-pong when their father comes back home tomorrow.",
  },
 {
        "right": "shall have been working",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "shall work",
            "have been working",
            "shall be working"
          ]
        },
        "question": "By Christmas, I... for you for 6 months.",
  },
 {
        "right": "am",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "am being",
            "was being",
            "have been being"
          ]
        },
        "question": "I...in the room now.",
  },







////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },
 {
        "right": "eat",
        "wrong":  
          [
            "eats",
            "are eating",
            "is eating"
          ]
        },
        "question": "My parents normally .... breakfast at 7:00 a.m.",
  },

    
  {
        "correctoption": "option2",
        "options": {
          "option1": '(A) cook',
          "option2": '(B) cooks',
          "option3": '(C) are cooking',
          "option4": '(D) is cooking',
        },
        "question":"This week Barbara is away on business so Tom ... dinner for himself.",
      },
       {
        "correctoption": "option2",
        "options": {
          "option1": '(A) has rested - has been being',
          "option2": '(B) has been resting - has been',
          "option3": '(C) has been resting - has been being',
          "option4": '(D) has rested - has been',
        },
        "question": 'Mary...(rest) in the garden all day because she ... (be) ill.',
      },
      {
        "correctoption": 'option2',
        "options": {
          "option1": '(A) What',
          "option2": '(B) How',
          "option3": '(C) Why',
          "option4": '(D) When',
        },
        "question": '...did the writer feel? Angry',
      },
       {
        "correctoption": 'option4',
        "options": {
          "option1": '(A) have spoken',
          "option2": '(B) has spoken ',
          "option3": '(C) have not been speaking',
          "option4": '(D) has not been speaking',
        },
        question:
          'He ...(not/speak) on the phone for half an hour, just a couple of minutes.',
      },
    },
  },
   quiz: {
    quiz1: {
      question1: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) ten years ago',
          option2: '(B) since ten years',
          option3: '(C) for ten years ago',
          option4: '(D) for ten years',
        },
        question: 'He has been selling motorcrycles....',
      },
      question2: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) discovered',
          option2: '(B) has discovered',
          option3: '(C) had discovered',
          option4: '(D) discovers',
        },
        question:
          'Columbus.... America more than 400 years ago.',
      },
      question3: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) run',
          option2: '(B) runs',
          option3: '(C) was running',
          option4: '(D) had run',
        },
        question: 'He fell down when he.... towards the church.',
      },
      question4: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) still lives',
          option2: '(B) still lived',
          option3: '(C) was still living',
          option4: '(D) were still living',
        },
        question: 'We....there when our father died',
      },
      question5: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) will play',
          option2: '(B) will be play ',
          option3: '(C) play',
          option4: '(D) would play',
        },
        question:
          'children...ping-pong when their father comes back home tomorrow.',
      },
      question6: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) shall have been working',
          option2: '(B) shall work ',
          option3: '(C) have been working',
          option4: '(D) shall be working',
        },
        question:
          'By Christmas, I... for you for 6 months.',
      },
      question7: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) am being',
          option2: '(B) was being ',
          option3: '(C) have been being',
          option4: '(D) am',
        },
        question:
          'I...in the room now.',
      },
    },
  },
  quiz: {
    quiz1: {
      question1: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) must',
          option2: '(B) had better',
          option3: '(C) can',
         
        },
        question: 'Ted is flight from amsterdam took more than 11 hours. He...be exhausted after such a long flight.',
      },
      question2: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) can not',
          option2: '(B) dont have to',
          option3: '(C) must not',
          
        },
        question:
          'The book is optional. My professor said we could read it if we needed extra credit. But we...read it if we dont want to.',
      },
      question3: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: "(A) couldn't",
          option2: "(B) can't",
          option3: '(C) might not',
          
        },
        question: 'Susan...hear the speaker because the crowd was cheering so loudly.',
      },
      question4: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) must be',
          option2: '(B) must have been',
          option3: '(C) must',
        },
        question: 'The television is not working. it....dameged during the move',
      },
      question5: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) will play',
          option2: '(B) will be play ',
          option3: '(C) play',
          option4: '(D) would play',
        },
        question:
          'children...ping-pong when their father comes back home tomorrow.',
      },
      question6: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) shall have been working',
          option2: '(B) shall work ',
          option3: '(C) have been working',
          option4: '(D) shall be working',
        },
        question:
          'By Christmas, I... for you for 6 months.',
      },
      question7: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) am being',
          option2: '(B) was being ',
          option3: '(C) have been being',
          option4: '(D) am',
        },
        question:
          'I...in the room now.',
      },
    },
  },
   quiz: {
    quiz1: {
      question1: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) along',
          option2: '(B) up',
          option3: '(C) away',
          option4: '(D) on',
        },
        question: 'No students can get.... with cheating in the exam.the teacher said',
      },
      question2: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) gazed',
          option2: '(B) stared',
          option3: '(C) glanced',
          option4: '(D) glared',
        },
        question:
          'He said he couldn’t give me a detailed description of the man because he had only .... at him briefly',
      },
      question3: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) saw',
          option2: '(B) see',
          option3: '(C) had seen',
          option4: '(D) have seen',
        },
        question: 'The children ran away as if they.... a ghost.',
      },
      question4: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) hardly',
          option2: '(B) nearly',
          option3: '(C) almost',
          option4: '(D) simply',
        },
        question: 'We were so late that we...had time to catch the train.',
      },
      question5: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) not involved',
          option2: '(B) were not involved ',
          option3: '(C) will not be involved',
          option4: '(D) wouldn’t be involved',
        },
        question: 'Frankly, I’d rather you .....in that case.',
      },
      question6: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) the',
          option2: '(B) what',
          option3: '(C) which',
          option4: '(D) those',
        },
        question:   'Most of ....archaeologists know about prehistoric cultures is based on studies of material remains.',
      },
      question7: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) disgrace',
          option2: '(B) shame ',
          option3: '(C) dishonor',
          option4: '(D) pity',
        },
        question:
          'He was expecting a prison sentence but the judge took .... on him.',
      },
      question8: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) are taken',
          option2: '(B) were taken ',
          option3: '(C) should be taken',
          option4: '(D) should have been taken',
        },
        question:
          'It is high time that measures .... to prevent further traffic accidents.',
      },
      question9: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) don’t you',
          option2: '(B) won’t you ',
          option3: '(C) will you',
          option4: '(D) do you',
        },
        question:
          'Don’t drop litter wherever you want, ......?',
      },
    },
  },
  quiz: {
    quiz1: {
      question1: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) has reviewed',
          option2: '(B) had reviewed',
          option3: '(C) will review',
          option4: '(D) reviewed',
        },
        question: ' If he ......the lesson yesterday, he could have done the test better',
      },
      question2: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) were mending - was pouring',
          option2: '(B) mended - poured',
          option3: '(C) mended - was pouring',
          option4: '(D) were mending - poured',
        },
        question:
          'We .... the roof for Mrs. Smith, an elderly childless woman, when it ....with rain.',
      },
      question3: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) cover',
          option2: '(B) covered',
          option3: '(C) covering',
          option4: '(D) to cover',
        },
        question: 'A correction pen is used for....your writing mistakes.',
      },
      question4: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) will she',
          option2: '(B) does she',
          option3: '(C) did she',
          option4: '(D) has she',
        },
        question: 'Your sister won’t go on vacation, ______?',
      },
      question5: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) got off',
          option2: '(B) come apart ',
          option3: '(C) broke down',
          option4: '(D) set out',
        },
        question:
          'The bus ....on the way here, so I was half an hour late for my appointment.',
      },
      question6: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) a',
          option2: '(B) an ',
          option3: '(C) the',
          option4: '(D) Ø (no article)',
        },
        question:
          'You do not usually have to go to...hospital to have your ears cleaned.',
      },
      question7: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) annoy',
          option2: '(B) have ',
          option3: '(C) see',
          option4: '(D) take',
        },
        question:
          'I hope you .... the point of everything your father and I have done for you.',
      },
      question8: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) fish',
          option2: '(B) duck ',
          option3: '(C) baby',
          option4: '(D) child',
        },
        question:
          'Sometimes in a bad situation, there may still be some good things. Try not tothrow the.... out with the bathwater.',
      },
      question9: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) brand',
          option2: '(B) model ',
          option3: '(C) trademark',
          option4: '(D) logo',
        },
        question:
          'There are so many .... names now that it is impossible to remember themall.',
      },
      question10: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) yet ',
          option2: '(B) although  ',
          option3: '(C) so that',
          option4: '(D) because',
        },
        question:
          'The use of computers aids in teaching, ... the role of teachers is still veryimportant.',
      },
    },
  },
  quiz: {
    quiz1: {
      question1: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) ten years ago',
          option2: '(B) since ten years',
          option3: '(C) for ten years ago',
          option4: '(D) for ten years',
        },
        question: 'He has been selling motorcrycles....',
      },
      question2: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) discovered',
          option2: '(B) has discovered',
          option3: '(C) had discovered',
          option4: '(D) discovers',
        },
        question:
          'Columbus.... America more than 400 years ago.',
      },
      question3: {
        correctoption: 'option3',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) run',
          option2: '(B) runs',
          option3: '(C) was running',
          option4: '(D) had run',
        },
        question: 'He fell down when he.... towards the church.',
      },
      question4: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) still lives',
          option2: '(B) still lived',
          option3: '(C) was still living',
          option4: '(D) were still living',
        },
        question: 'We....there when our father died',
      },
      question5: {
        correctoption: 'option2',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) will play',
          option2: '(B) will be play ',
          option3: '(C) play',
          option4: '(D) would play',
        },
        question:
          'children...ping-pong when their father comes back home tomorrow.',
      },
      question6: {
        correctoption: 'option1',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) shall have been working',
          option2: '(B) shall work ',
          option3: '(C) have been working',
          option4: '(D) shall be working',
        },
        question:
          'By Christmas, I... for you for 6 months.',
      },
      question7: {
        correctoption: 'option4',
        options: {
          option1: '(A) am being',
          option2: '(B) was being ',
          option3: '(C) have been being',
          option4: '(D) am',
        },
        question:
          'I...in the room now.',
      },
    },
  },
]
